articlesshare.com 2015-09-08

# Articles sharing website to share articles and get paid for quality views on articles » Join us to share your thoughts , contents , articles , videos , audios and get paid for your articles, publish yourself by linking back to your source site » Privacy Policy

We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect, use and disclose when you visit our website . The guidelines contained herein apply to your visit or use of the Site.

## **_Acceptance of the Policy_**

**_PLEASE READ CAREFULLY_** : BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.

## **_How do we collect information on our Users?_**

_There are two main methods we use:_

**a. We collect information while you access, browse, view or otherwise use the Site**. In other words, when you access the Site we are aware of your usage of the Site, and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage. For example, when you connect to the Site, your computer tells us your IP address.

**b. We collect information which you provide us voluntarily.** For example, when you wish to register to the Site, we may ask you to provide certain Personal Information which shall be kept on our servers. Each time you will be interested in providing information voluntarily we may ask you to consent to the collection and public display of such information.

## **_What are the purposes of collecting the information?_**

_Non-personal Information is collected in order to:_

  * enhance the User’s experience on the Site (e.g. by determining the screen resolutions).
  * learn about the preferences of Users and general trends on our Site (e.g. understand which software is more popular than others).
  * better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.
  * administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information.

_Personal Information is collected in order to:_

  * personalize your experience on the Site.
  * provide you with certain information and services available only to registered Users.
  * allow us to contact you with proposals and tailored information regarding events, offers, etc.
  * identify you when conducting customer service operations (such as license purchase and generation, providing product feedback, etc.).
  * other User Generated Content, voluntarily supplied by the User for the purpose of public use and display (e.g. public User Bio).

## **_Sharing Personal Information with third parties_**

We will share Personal Information only in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce these Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to claims that any content published on the Site violates any right of a third-party; (e) to respond to claims that unauthorized information (e.g. e-mail address, name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Site by us without your consent; (f) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its Users or the general public; (g) when Company is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Company; (h) pursuant to your approval, in order to supply certain services you have requested from Company; (i) to let our partners and affiliates serve you with commercials; or (j) with respect to articles, opinions, any other documentation supplied by you for the purpose of public use, in order to provide the services.

## **_Cookies & Local Storage_**

When you visit the Site, Company may use industry-wide technologies such as “Cookies” (or similar technologies), which stores certain information on your computer (“ **Local Storage** “) and which will allow us to enable automatic sign-in to the Site, and make your browsing much more convenient and effortless. For example, and for your convenience, a Cookie can “autofill” information on forms on the Site, precluding the need for you to fill out the same information on our registration forms each time you want to access information that requires registration. However, cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user; It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored.

We also use certain third-party cookies. These are a different kind of cookies, which are stored on your computer by a third party site, rather than by the Company. This kind of cookie is updated each time you visit our Site, and also when you visit other website that uses similar cookies. Third-party cookies usually store only a Non-personal Information, such as the web pages you have visited, the duration of your browsing, etc.

## **_Security_**

We take a great care in maintaining the security of the Site and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

Users who have registered to the Site agree to keep their password in strict confidence and not disclose such password to any third party.

## **_Third Party Sites_**

While using the Site you may encounter links to third party websites. Please be advised that such third party websites are independent sites, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites.

## **_Changes to the Privacy Policy_**

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected therein. Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. In case of any material change, we will post a clear notice on the Site.
